hentaimedia.com 2008-09-03

# Hentai Media

**Hentai Media Privacy Notice**

Hentai Media recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others who use [www.HentaiMedia.com](http://www.hentaimedia.com/) or other   
web sites owned or operated by Hentai Media value their privacy. This Privacy Notice details important information regarding   
the use and disclosure of User information collected on the Hentai Media site. Hentai Media provides this Privacy Notice to   
help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the Hentai Media site.

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Terms of Use. Your use of the Hentai Media site and any   
personal information you provide on the Hentai Media site remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use.

Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the Hentai Media site becomes   
published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Notice.

**All Information Hentai Media Collects  
**

  * User Provided Information: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to   
Hentai Media when choosing to participate in various activities on the Hentai Media site such as uploading videos, posting messages   
in our forums or in the video comments section, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to   
surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists.  

  * Cookies Information: When you visit the Hentai Media site, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a   
string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Hentai Media uses both   
session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be   
used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser  
help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web   
browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the   
Hentai Media site may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.  

  * Log File Information: When you use the Hentai Media site, our servers automatically record certain information that   
your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request,  
Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type,   
number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on   
particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
  * **What Hentai Media Uses Information for**

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the Hentai Media site, then we use your personal information  
to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Hentai Media site.

  * Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas,  
within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.   
Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload videos or send messages through the  
Hentai Media site and other Users can contact you through messages and comments.   
Any videos that you submit to the Hentai Media site may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels,   
and may be viewed by the general public.  

  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages   
without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.  
We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying  
you of major Hentai Media Site changes or for customer service purposes).  

  * We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous  
User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Hentai Media  
site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.  

  * We use cookies and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or  
the next time you visit the Hentai Media site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of   
our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and   
(e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

**Will Hentai Media Discloses Information  
**

  * We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies,  
or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to  
process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information  
and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  

  * We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for  
their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you   
will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.  

  * We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs,  
platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for   
certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Hentai Media site.  

  * We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law,  
or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law)  
or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.  

  * Hentai Media also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable   
information that Hentai Media believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use,   
take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist  
government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property,  
or personal safety of Hentai Media, our Users or others.

**Your Options  
**

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Hentai Media site, in which   
case Hentai Media may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal profile  
information and email preferences at any time by visiting your [account profile page](http://www.hentaimedia.com/members/action/myprofile/). Please note that media files uploaded  
by Users to the Hentai Media site cannot be removed and remain subject to our Terms of Use.  

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity  
before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique  
password and account information at all times.  

Please contact Hentai Media with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information,  
your consent, or your opt-in or opt-out choices using this [contact form](http://www.hentaimedia.com/action/contactus/).

**Third-party Advertisers & Links to Other sites  
**

Hentai Media allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the   
Hentai Media site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser,   
the advertisements and links that appear on the Hentai Media site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens.  
They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of   
their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.  

Hentai Media does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without   
your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.   
However, please note that if an advertiser asks Hentai Media to show an advertisement to a certain audience   
(for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content)  
and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they  
are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Hentai Media site, such as the number of   
times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.  

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on  
their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Hentai Media's privacy policy does not apply to,  
and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web site.

**  
Our Commitment To Childrens' Privacy  
**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Hentai Media does not knowingly collect  
or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the Hentai Media site from   
persons under 18 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 18. If you are under 18 years of age,  
then please do not use or access the Hentai Media site at any time or in any manner. If Hentai Media learns that personally   
identifiable information of persons under 18 years of age has been collected on the Hentai Media site without verified parental   
consent, then Hentai Media will take the appropriate steps to delete this user/information.

**Notes to International Users  
**

The Hentai Media site intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the Hentai Media site   
from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure,  
that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Hentai Media site, which are   
governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States  
and you consent to that transfer.

**In the Event of Sale, Bankruptc or Joint Ventures  
**

In the event that Hentai Media is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances,  
to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.  
In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the   
application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal   
information is treated, transferred, or used.

**  
Updates to this Privacy Notice  
**

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "effective date" below. Please revisit this page to stay   
aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when   
we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the Hentai Media site constitutes your agreement to   
this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.  

For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personal information you   
have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information.  

**Date Last Modified:**  
This Privacy Notice was last modified September 28, 2007.  

**Contact Information:**  
Please contact Hentai Media with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice using this [contact form](http://www.hentaimedia.com/action/contactus/).
